Amen. Amen. Greetings and welcome to
Living Mana's power line, your
connection to the throne. No matter
what's going on, no matter where you
are, no matter who you are or what
you're going through, log in, tune in,
let us pray for you, let us stand in the
gap because that's what God has called
us to do. Greetings and welcome to
Living Man of Power. Amen. So, let me
try and turn this down. We got some
stuff going.
Okay, we're working out some kinks here
tonight.
Okay,
I know, Gigi. I'm laughing, too. Yeah,
laugh about these echoes we have. But
listen, we're we're here tonight to
pray. No matter what's going on, we we
won't forget that again. So, uh anyway,
I'm Brother Terry, as you all know. This
is my lovely bride Amra and we're
manning the power line
uh ministry endeavor by Living Mana
online church and we're thankful to God
to be here tonight to pray for you.
We're going to be for the next half hour
taking live prayer request. So want to
invite you to log in and join us. Uh hit
that like button, subscribe, hit the
notification, share the link with
somebody you know, and don't forget put
your prayer requests in the chat. We're
going to be praying for you live
tonight. And so what I want to ask my
lovely bride to do is to start us off
with an opening prayer. And after that,
we're going to get right into taking
your prayer request.
Yes. Lord Jesus, I just want to thank
you for this evening. Thank you, Lord,
for this opportunity to just pray over
anyone who needs prayer for their loved
ones, for themselves. Um, no prayer is
too small or too big for you, Lord. So,
we just look forward to interceding for
anyone in need. And um we just lift this
uh time together up to you that it be a
blessed uh experience. In Jesus name I
pray. Amen. Amen. Amen. So, we're going
to start off tonight with uh a prayer
request from Sister Sharon Faith Johnson
who who wrote in and uh uh she said she
spoke with her attorney and is her
attorney's office and found um that uh
Progressive Insurance does not want to
settle the claim for a terrible terrible
car accident she had in January 9, 2024
and one of the injured drivers and by
one of the injured drivers. She says
she's requesting prayer for this matter
as well as a fair settlement. And so we
want to thank you, Sister Sharon. We see
you tonight, Sister Sharon, there in
that chat. We're praying for you and
that the Lord will settle. We see you
there. And so, Father, we just want to
thank you as we continue to uh offer up
prayer tonight. Lord, we're standing in
the gap for everyone that's calling in.
This is the power line and we want to
thank you for the opportunity to
intercede for your people. Lord, you are
the God that executes righteousness and
judgment for all who are oppressed. So,
thank you for standing in the gap for
Sister Sharon. Also, we have a prayer
request uh from Sister Gigi who's
requesting prayer for Sister Jennifer
Booth who's in the ER with a um diabetic
ketosis and she's being transferred to
the ICU. She had to put her dog to sleep
last week. So, it's been really rough.
And so, Lord, we want to thank you. We
have been praying for Sister Jennifer.
Lord, we thank you that you're on the
case. We thank you that you're working
in and through her life. Lord, continue
to bless her. Continue, Lord, to be
there for her, Lord, in Jesus name. and
God, Sister Jennifer, Lord God, who has
been a servant for you. Uh we also want
to remember uh brother Derek Burgess. He
says, "Please keep us in uh uh pray for
our son PJ. He was homeschooled and very
active in the church until he went away
to university and changed. Stopped
communicating with the entire family
eight years ago. And his parents only
communication via email when he is in
need. And so they they're asking prayer
for him that uh he's been somewhat
disrespectful and file and vengeful and
bitter and a little bit accusatory. And
so they they're asking for prayer uh uh
that we would uh continue to to lift him
up. Um they haven't actually seen him in
eight years. And so we we want to
continue to lift uh uh this beautiful
family up Lord in Jesus name. Lord your
word says train up a child in the way
that he should go and when he uh is old
he will not depart from it Lord God. and
from the time of childhood to getting
old, there are some lessons to be
learned. We pray that you will
intervene, Lord, in this family's life.
Give them hope, Lord, and give them uh
security and faith to trust in you and
in your word. Lord, strengthen them to
continue to stand on your word and
believe in you no matter what they see,
no matter what they hear. Give them a
heart of love to continue to love
through the rough times and through the
hard times in Jesus name. God breathe
with brother PJ in a special way. bless
his life and touch his life in Jesus
name. And God, sister Pat Patton Mon add
to that prayer. Lord, I just lift up
PJ's mental health to you. He was also
diagnosed with delusional disorder and
schizophrenia and he is refusing to
accept that diagnosis. And so, Lord, we
pray that you just remove any scales
from his eyes, that he will know that he
needs a mental health professional to
help guide him, Lord, and that he um
will be in a healthy, mentally healthy,
stable place very soon. Amen. Amen.
Amen. And North has put a live prayer
request in the chat and she says, "Pre,
please pray that my family will accept
Jesus." Amen. And father, we want to
thank you for Sister North who is uh
standing in the gap to intercede for her
family. Your word says that you set the
solitary in families and you bring out
those who are bound in chains, Lord. And
so we thank you. You also said in your
word, Lord, believe in the Lord Jesus
and you shall be saved. You and your
whole household. You didn't only say
that to the Philippian jailer, but
you're saying that to all of us who will
trust you and stand in the gap for our
families and for our loved ones, Lord.
And so we pray and lift her family up
before you tonight, believing in you by
faith. God, we thank you. This is not a
coincidence that she's here tonight
praying for her family on the power
line. Lord, we thank you that you've
given us direct access to the throne of
grace in order that we might obtain
mercy and find grace to help in time of
need. And so we just bless you and lift
you up and praise you in Jesus name.
Amen. Amen.
And Lord, I'm going to continue to pray
uh for Pat Mree, who is praying for
strength for uh Jakara and healing for
her mom, Yolanda, who is in um the
hospital due to a pneumonia and she has
a blood clot in her lungs. And so we're
going to continue to lift her up with
that. Uh we also want to continue to
pray for her grandmother, Paty, who is
battling an aggressive cancer. and um
she still can't find her son who's been
uh missing for five weeks. And so now
and and and now her daughter Yolanda.
And so Lord, we lift up this precious
family. Lord, we lift up healing for
cancer. Lord God, we also pray, Lord,
that you would bring reconciliation and
healing. Help them to find loved ones
that are are missing. God, we know,
Lord, that you know everything, Lord.
You sit high and look low. Your word
says your eyes run to and fro throughout
the whole earth and showing yourself
perfect in behalf of those whose hearts
are perfect toward you. And so Lord,
tonight we thank you God that your ear
is attentive. We thank you for the
opportunity to pray for these precious
loved ones Lord God in Jesus glorious
name. And thank you for this opportunity
tonight, Lord God, to man the power
line, to be able to stand in the gap,
for all those who are viewing, for all
those who would write in, Lord, for all
those who would share the link with
others, Lord God, that they might find
hope and find answers to prayer in Jesus
name. Amen. Amen. Joanne is asking for
prayer for the guy I met on the street
who was just discharged from the
hospital and has no cash nor means of
feeding his family and was distraught.
Pray. pray the Lord provides and give
him a job and hope. Amen. Amen.
Lord, I just want to pray for this man.
God, I just pray that you bless him in a
special way. I pray that you give him
the health care and the financial um
blessing that he needs, Lord. I pray
that you comfort his mind and his
spirit, God, and that you provide him
with a job, that you provide him with
hope, and that he can um know that he
can trust in you in all things. Amen.
Sister Ramona Baddy is reminding us to
pray for everyone who's having to deal
with the tornadoes and the devastation
in the south. And Lord, we thank you,
God, uh that you will be a hedge about
your people. want to thank you for this
precious sister, Lord God, being mindful
of others who are going through
struggles and trials and that you will
stand with them tonight in a special way
and also stand with our sister Ramona
who is our family and our loved one,
Lord God. And we thank you for her. We
thank you for her heart of service. We
thank you for her love, Lord. And thank
you for your grace in her life in Jesus
name. Amen. Amen. All right, Wendy
Allen, please pray for me. I have been
sick for 10 days. Wendy, we just lift
you up in prayer right now. We pray that
the Lord bless your body and your
healing. We thank you that you shared
your prayer request with us, Lord. And
we just pray for God, the almighty
healer, um to intercede on your behalf
in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Amen. trying
to go through as our sister Nicole is
asking that we would pray uh for her
friend Julie who is in need uh of a
breakthrough in health and her finances.
Uh she needs a special touch from the
Lord. And so we do want to re uh
remember our beloved sister Nicole who
is a dear member of Living Mana. And we
we thank you, Nicole, for tuning in
tonight and for sharing this prayer
request for your friend, Julie, who's in
need of a breakthrough in her health and
in her finances. Uh and and so, Father,
we know that you uh uh are always
touched with the feelings of our
infirmities. Thank you, God, that the
apostle said, "But my God shall supply
all of your needs according to his
riches in glory in Christ Jesus." And
Father, we know that you're able. uh you
we see Julie, Lord God, and you know her
need in this hour. Lord, we don't
believe in coincidences. Lord, we
believe, Lord God, that you're allowing
your people, your members, your church,
your body to be your hands and feet. And
so, Lord, thank you for touching the
heart of uh Nicole and putting Nicole in
just the right place at the right time
to see the need for Julie and to type
this prayer request on the power line
tonight. Lord, we want to thank you in
advance and give you all of the glory,
all of the honor, and all of the praise
for you are still a miracle working God.
And Lord, want to thank you for this
power line while we're praying right
now. Want to thank you for our our
production team and Sister Gigi and
those working behind the scenes to bring
us live tonight, Lord God, for the first
time, Lord. And we already seeing this
was supposed to be a brief test run, but
we're already seeing God. Hallelujah.
That the your people are already filling
up these chats. And I pray, Lord, for
those who will like and those who will
share the link and for those who will
reach out, Lord, I want to thank you for
our pastor, for the vision of his heart,
Lord. What an amazing gift and a vessel,
Lord. And so, Lord, just bring folk in,
Lord, and help us to be prepared. I want
to pray for the the prayer warriors who
will be manning this power line, Lord
God. on different prayer warriors who
will be here teams and will be working
together and be make giving themselves
unto you Lord God for those who will be
fasting and praying and believing for
breakthrough that we will have anointing
and power and discernment in our lives
to make a difference for those we pray
for we give you the glory honor and
praise in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. We
have a prayer request for Atante our
first lady. Yes. Please pray. I have an
important meeting tomorrow. Would you
like to pray for her? Amen. Amen.
Father, we thank you for our first lady.
We thank you, Lord God, for I mean, just
beautiful inside and out, Lord God.
Gifted and talented, Lord God. And we
thank you. We are honored to be able to
serve her and to pray for her, Lord God.
She has an important me important
meeting tomorrow, Lord. We want to thank
you that you have gone before her to
prepare her way. Thank you for the
angels that you have encamped about her.
Lord, thank you for your incredible
giftedness in her life as a wife, as a
mother, Lord, as a spiritual mother to
all of us, oh God. And we thank you,
God, over and over for uh such a
beautiful uh uh vessel unto you, Lord,
in Jesus glorious name. Amen. Amen.
Next, we have a prayer request from
H. Hello, brethren. My name is Edwin.
Hello, Edwin. Things are tough. Sales
haven't been coming through. My brother
is currently looking for work. Amen.
Amen. Should I pray or would you like to
pray? Go ahead. We're switching it off
and we are a team and so we thank God
for well, you know, we thank God for the
tandem team that we have and some of the
tandem teams you'll be seeing. We look
forward to the night when uh even pastor
and first lady come on and man the power
line. And you already know they're a
power team. But brother Edwin, listen.
Our God is an amazing God. And tonight,
he's brought you here to Living Manners
Power Line to bless your life. Don't
forget to come back and tell us how God
has answered your prayers. And so, Lord,
we lift everyone up before you. And we
just thank you for him, Lord God. Lord,
we know that you own the cattle on a
thousand hill. Lord, there are promises
in your word, Lord, for every situation
that we will ever face in life. Your
word said, "According as your divine
power has given unto us all things that
pertain unto life and godliness, through
the knowledge of him who hath called us
to glory and virtue, that by these
exceeding precious promises, hallelujah,
we might be partakers of the divine
nature, having escaped the corruption
that is in the world through lust."
Lord, we pray in Jesus name that Edwin's
eyes would be open to see and to know,
God, that you have provided for him. The
spirit of prophecy says you have a
thousand ways to provide for us that we
know not of. And so Lord, we pray that
he would just bump into his blessing as
he holds on to you and continues to
trust in you, Lord God. In Jesus name,
work miracles in Edwin's life, Lord God,
that he will know the God of heaven
still hears and answers prayer in Jesus
name.
Amen. Ramona Batty is asking for prayer
um for all those who are dealing with
tornado devastation. Amen. That one
already came up. We prayed for that one.
Okay. And there's a prayer for our
beloved sister Majesa has one there. It
says, "Plea, please pray for a mother
refugee with two children that have been
sent away u from the refugee camp and
denied asylum and are now on the
streets. Lord have mercy." Oh, there
was. Would you pray for that, please?
Sorry. There was one that she posted
ahead of that. I was
I'll get that one if you'll pray for
this one. Okay.
Lord Jesus, I just pray for this mother
and there and uh two children who have
been sent away from the refugee camp and
denied asylum and housing. Lord, um
Jesus, I just pray that you that you
intercede, that you intervene, give them
shelter, give them food, give them
resources, give them everything that
they need to be able to take care of
themselves. I pray that you soften the
heart for those who are in charge of
this um refugee camp. Lord, let her in.
Let her children in. And I just pray
that you provide her with a care and
that somehow she knows that it is coming
from you in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. So,
Majesca's other
one, please pray for a sister from Sudan
that appeared at church today that is
homeless and has nowhere to go that you
may open ways for her and provide for
her. Keep her safe tonight and bless
her. Amen. You want to take that one?
Yes, Father, we want to thank you, God,
for hearing the our prayers for this
sister from Sudan who appeared in
church. And and and we thank you, Lord
God. You you we know that you are a
father to the fatherless, Lord God.
You're a shelter to those who are
homeless, Lord. You are friend that
stickketh closer than a brother. And we
want to thank you for hearing our
prayers tonight for this precious soul.
Lord God, heal her, save her, touch her,
and deliver her. Keep her safe tonight.
Encamp your angels about her. Oh God, we
trust in you and we plead the blood of
Jesus upon her, around her tonight, Lord
God, between her and any harm. We give
you glory, honor, and praise for hearing
and answering, Lord. Amen. Amen. From
Gina
Brower, please pray our new dog Jesse
will be comfortable in our home and know
we are for her. Also to stop head
tremors she sometimes has. Well, first
off, Gina, congratulations on your new
puppy son.
Amen.
We love our dogs here. So, let me pray.
Amen. Lord Jesus, I just want to praise
you, God, for um this new pet, this new
family member that Gina and Ross can
enjoy in their home. We pray that um
Jesse will just acclimate and be
comfortable and feel at home. Lord, I
know it takes a little while for dogs to
adjust and know that this is their
permanent home. And so I pray that comes
sooner than later that this dog will
trust them, that the dog will know that
that they are provided for, that they
will have a soft landing for their head
and food in their belly and lots of love
and cuddles and comfort. And we just
thank you for Gina and Ross for taking
this dog in in Jesus name. Amen. And
amen. Amen. Sharon Reed is here and
she's saying, "Pray for my cousin had
they had a stroke last year and just got
going through uh many mental changes and
physical changes and also uh uh help us
Jesus please." And so, Sister Sharon
Reed, thank you so much uh for allowing
us to to stand in the gap and share in
your struggle here on the power line.
Lord, we want to thank you, God. Lord,
thank you so much. This is not just a
program called the power line. We are
the lifeline. You have given us God a
charge. You've given us a call on our
lives and you have Lord been mindful of
us Lord. Who are we God? That you would
be mindful of us and allow us to be
partakers of this incredible gift. Lord,
we pray in Jesus' name that Sister
Sharon would know that she is loved and
that she is cherished and that those
loved ones who are going through strange
uh changes and going through mental
challenges would know, Lord God. May she
be a link between you and them. May she
be the bridge, Lord, to show them love
and show them compassion, Lord God. God.
And I pray you bring Sister Sharon right
back here, Lord God, to Living Mana to
testify of just how good you've been.
How you've heard and answered prayers
and how you've turned it all around.
Lord, we've seen you turn it around in
our lives. And we know you're no
respector of persons. You will do it for
us. You will do it for her. And so we
give you the glory, honor, and praise
tonight in Jesus name. Amen. Amen. Amen.
Let me grab the next one.
Oh, for the regulars in church in uh
from Living Mana, don't forget that
Power Wednesday started at 4 well about
20 minutes ago if um you need to go and
come
back. Um next up we have
Barbara. Please pray for Megan who is in
the bondage of addiction. Lord, we know
this too well, unfortunately. And we
just we pray that you break the chain of
addiction in um Megan's life, Lord. I
pray that she um will be able to fill
that void in her heart that she is
filling up with um substances, God.
Amen. Um, I just pray God that you fill
her with the Holy Spirit so much that
she can't handle all the love that she's
experiencing from you. I pray that she
gets guidance and um help, Lord. Um,
that she will go into an addiction
program with sponsors and people that
will help her through this journey. That
she has a community around her that will
help her through her addiction, Lord.
And you know, you have to come to the
point where you are ready for help. And
so I pray, Lord, that you impress on her
um that she will be ready, Lord. And I
just lift that up in prayer in Jesus
name. Amen. Amen. Amen. From Jodie
Mccclure, please pray that pastor and
are safe and for me because I'm getting
attacked again. You want to take them?
Amen. Amen. Father, we want to thank you
for our beloved sister Jodie. Lord, and
um Lord, I just pray that you grant her
uh an awesome revelation, Lord, that she
would see this struggle, this challenge
from your perspective. Not one of us who
is a child of God is under attack. We're
over attack because you said that we've
been raised up to sit together in
heavenly places far above all
principality and power and might and
dominion and every name that is named,
not only in in in in he in the earth,
but also in heaven. And so we thank you,
Lord, that Jesus, Lord God, would be
manifested to Jod in a special way in
the midst of this trial and that she
would see that she's fighting from a
position of victory. Lord, give her
peace, give her faith, and give her
strength and protect and keep her in
Jesus name we pray. Amen. Amen. Lisa
Clark, hi So and prayer team. Hello.
Good to see you. Praising God for giving
my niece a promotion this week after a
challenging time at work. Please pray
for the Lord's support for her in this
new role. Lord Jesus, I just want to
lift up Lisa's niece. God, I praise you,
Lord, for this new position. I praise
you, Lord, that she has um the resource
to be able to work. Um and we just thank
you for that, God. I pray that you give
her confidence in her new role. I pray
that you open her mind to be able to
retain all the new information that
she's learning and needs to pick up.
God, I pray that her um employers will
see her value. Lord, that they um will
feel good about selecting her for that
role and that she will excel and exceed
in that. Lord, we pray and thank you for
her and um your goodness for putting her
in that position in Jesus name. Amen.
Amen. Amen. Um, just a moment here. I
want to want to we want to make a a
brief announcement as we continue to
pray. Uh, tonight's broadcast was
actually just sort of a test run. All
right? And not kind of like a rehearsal,
but I assure you there's nothing about
the prayer request you're putting in
that chat, the struggles and the child
trials that you're going through. That's
a rehearsal. God's showing up and God is
showing out and doing what he does in
and through your lives. And so, uh, it's
for real. These prayers are for real.
Our faith is real. We're calling on God
for real tonight. But we want to ask
you, would you pray for us? Pray for the
broadcast. Continue to pray for the
souls that will come in. Uh, we can see
already from just this little bit of
time we spent. Uh, you know, we're going
to be
[Music]
uh we're going to be shaping up and
getting it together and figuring out the
ins and outs. We're in a learning curve
right now. We are. We are. But and we
also want to we also want to ask you to
keep in prayer. Uh again, our warriors
will be manning the the the power line
just like you're seeing us do. And we
love them. Uh and they're they're are an
awesome bunch. They're the reason why we
have the confidence and the faith to do
what we do, you know, apart from Jesus.
But and also listen, I can't say it
enough. Sister Gigi is behind the scene
and I'm telling you right now, she's
helped us to pull it together just in
the nick of time. you you let me tell
you it it's amazing and I want to thank
uh pastor and attante uh uh it's this
for just being obedient to the vision
that the Lord has given saints we're
believing that the power line is going
to be one of the means that God's just
continues to bring in more and more
souls into the kingdom of God uh by way
of living mana and so uh thank you for
allowing us to be a part of you your
lives thank you for allowing us to pray
for you as you pray for us and listen
Let's build meaningful relationships.
Share the link, like, subscribe, get the
word out. Hey, share the mana. Let
everybody know. Living man is going to
be praying, taking live prayer requests.
And uh we don't know how long we gonna
go on, but uh glory to God. Sister
Sharon Fay, we see you there in the
chat. We also pans up. Well, we also
want to remind you that if for some
reason we do not um mention your prayer
request live, we have our prayer
warriors in the chat collecting them and
rest
assured they will be prayed for
throughout the week. And so your prayers
are covered uh no matter what. Yeah. And
and uh Sister Donna Elise, we're not
going to forget your prayer request
tonight. I'll see it in the chat. There
will be times, I'm going to tell you
where we're probably going to be
bombarded. There's no way we'll get them
all live. But I will assure you that the
living man of prayer warriors, they're
going to be manning that chat. Also, we
have Power Wednesday going on
simultaneously because we know that uh
we're going to be reaching some other
people to just go and fill up Power
Wednesday. Yes. Let me read Donna's
prayer request and then you can pray for
her. Yes, ma'am.
Please pray for my son to call me and
for me to gain a blessing from fasting
from media for 10 days to please find a
place in the country that fits my needs
and my nephew who was beaten up. Amen.
Sister Donna, praise God. We're going to
pray for you now. And you know, I was
that son that needed to call home and
and God brought me home and and had me
call my mom. Uh so he will call you and
we want to trust God to hear and answer
your prayer. pray. We also want to pray
for the the young man who was beaten up.
And Father, we thank you, Lord, in the
name of Jesus. Lord, you're able to turn
tragedy into triumph, Lord God. Trials
into victories, Lord God. Messes into
messages, Lord. You're These are not
just cliches and colorful cute little
things to say. You're in the business of
turning lives around. You're in the
business of saving lives. Lord God, I am
a wi living witness tonight that you you
do save from the guttermost to the
uttermost, Lord. And I want to thank you
for that, for reaching down. And Lord,
as no respector of persons, you did it
for me. I know you will do it for these
young men. Lord, may that mother who's
waiting by that phone to hear a call
from her son, Lord God, who she loves,
Lord. Nothing like a mother's love. And
Lord, hear her prayers, answer her
prayers tonight. we join our faith with
her, Lord, that he would call his
mother, Lord God, and and affirm his
love and speak with her and con converse
with her, Lord, in Jesus name. You're
the God of reconciliation and so
reconcile in that family. Heal hurts,
Lord God. Men wounds, Lord, we pray this
in Jesus mighty and majestic name. Amen.
Amen.
Majesca is saying, "Please thank God for
providing and opening ways for me and
helping me out for my situation, my
travels, and bringing bringing me back
home safely." Amen. Did Did we remember
Lisa's niece who got the promotion? Her
name is Raina. Raina got a promotion.
So, we're praising God, too. And my
sister's name is Raina spelled
differently, but yes, it is. I love that
name.
Listen, this just went too fast. It did.
You want to read my t-shirt? You know, a
tante does a t-shirt message and I
thought, you know, let me wear a t-shirt
with a message today in honor of you,
Atante. I'm not stealing your thunder.
But what does it say? I survived too
many storms to be bothered by raindrops.
Right.
I like the message. That's an awesome
message. which reminds us those storms
that we've gone through have prepared us
for what we're going through right now.
And want to remind you saints here as we
get ready to bring this program to a
close. But we'll be right back with you
on the power line uh uh uh uh next time,
Lord willing. And I want to remind you
of something. Listen, you've come
through a whole lot. And remember the
God who brought you through those past
trials and those past storms. Don't let
these little raindrops that you're
feeling right now in your life. And some
of you, we don't take your struggles or
trials lightly. That's why we're here
praying and standing in the gap. But God
is faithful. He's the same yesterday,
today, and forever. Amen. And he he
healed before, he can do it again. He
raised the dead before, he can do it
again. He opened blind eyes. He can do
it again. He healed the sick. He can do
it again. He caused the lame to run and
leap. He can do it again. He He fed
thousands in the wilderness. He can do
it again. And he will do it. And so keep
your faith up, saints. can join us again
next time right there on the power line.
Donna, Donna's upset.
Let me go through and thoroughly pray
for you, Donna. Hold on.
Did I miss something in that prayer
request?
Oh, we lift Donna up uh this evening,
Lord, again, and we want to make sure
that she gets all of her prayer requests
prayed over, Lord. So, we first want to
lift up her son to get in contact with
her, to call her, to We don't know
what's going on with their relationship,
Lord, but you are um someone who mends
fences. So, I just pray, Lord, that her
son will call her. I also pray for a
special blessing, Lord, from fasting,
for social media for 10 days. God,
we know that sometimes that can be
challenging as enticing as social media
can be, but we pray Lord that she can
spend that time that she would be on
social media um just spending time with
you Lord fellowshipping with you and um
bringing her prayer requests to you and
your praises to you as well. Amen. We
also f we also pray Lord that she find a
place in the country that fits her
needs. Um we lift that up. I think that
is what Terry prayed for. Um that you
just open a home that is suitable for
her and that brings her peace and uh
contentment, Lord. And I also
um we also lift up her nephew who was
recently beaten up. Um we don't know
what the circumstances was for that
either, but Lord, if he was hurt, we
pray for healing over his body. um if
he's
um just mentally hurt, we pray that you
do a healing in his mind and his spirit.
Um I pray that any situation that is a
tough one um will bring people closer to
you. So I just pray God that Donna and
her nephew and her son will will uh just
draw closer to you Lord in Jesus name.
Amen. Amen. Let let me
say, Sister Donna, I like you. You know
what? And and you have permission.
Anytime Brother Terry mess up like that,
come. Uhuh. Uhuh. Brother Terry, where
is the rest of my prayer request? I like
that. That's importunity. That's right.
Come on, saints. Help. We got to help
one another out, you know, and that's
why I have her, you know, cuz I just
chopped all through there. And see,
Donna is taking her prayer request
serious. She's not going to let me just
pick through there and pick out what she
wants me to be specific and to the
point. And thank you, sister, because
the Lord is very, very concerned about
your prayer request and he's going to
answer it specifically. So, thank you
all for that. No worries. Let's finish
and I am sorry. I am sorry. So, please
forgive me for making that mistake. We
have two more prayer requests in the
chat. We're going to cover that and then
we are going to say good night for the
evening. Majeska has one more prayer
request tonight. Please pray for the
conversion of my sister and her family,
my mom, my relatives, Dyron, Mela, and
friends. Amen. Amen. Which which one is
it? It's right
here. It's uh please pray for the
conversion of my sister and her family,
my mom, my relatives, Dyron, Mela, and
friends. Amen. And I just saw an
interesting note in the chat. It says,
"Sniper
prayers." Sniper prayers are detailed,
focused, and pinpointed prayers. And so,
Brother Terry ought to know better than
that, having been trained to be a sniper
prayer warrior,
right? We will do better, saints. And
so, Majesca has asked us, Father, to
pray for the conversion of her sister,
her family, her mom, her relatives,
Daren, Mela, and friends. And so, Lord,
we thank you that Lord, you have heard
this prayer request in detail. And we
thank you, God, that even before the
foundation of the world, you have made
provision to answer it specifically as
asked. You know these precious ones by
name. And thank you that their names are
written in the palm of your hands. Thank
you, oh Lord God, for this opportunity
tonight to lift them up before you and
to believe, Lord God, for you to
intervene in their lives in a special
way. Bring salvation to them, Lord.
Bring hope, bring that conversion, Lord
God, that you al you alone can do and
accomplish in their lives in Jesus name.
Amen. Amen. And Seb Grace, this is our
last prayer for the evening. Thank you
so much for being here with us. Seb
Grace asks for prayer for Samantha. She
needs to eat and it's hurting bad. I
just seen y'all were on. Please pray.
She's 95 pounds.
You want to finish the last prayer?
Amen. Lord, we want to lift up Sam
Samantha before you, Lord.
Lord, we know that uh she needs to eat
to live and she needs to gain that
weight, Lord God. Uh, Father, we pray
tonight that you would intervene, Lord,
and bring soothing and comfort to her
soul, Lord God. Uh, health to her flesh
and marrow to her bones, Lord. Lord, we
speak your word over her tonight, Lord.
We speak the words of faith and the
words of life over Samantha, Lord.
Samantha, Lord, Lord, we know you know
her by name. We know you have known her
before the foundation of the world,
Lord. Your word says you will bring
health and cure, and so do it in Jesus
name, God. We thank you that you are the
Lord, our healer. We thank you that you
are the Lord who hears and answers
prayers when we stand in faith, trusting
in you, Lord. And so we just lift her up
right now, God, in Jesus name, in a
special way. Thank you, God, for hearing
and answering this prayer in Jesus name.
Amen.
Well, we will be back next week, same
time, same place. We hope that you join
us again for the power line. Amen. Your
connection to the throne no matter
what's going on. God bless you, saints.
Amen. Good night, everyone.